你怎么了?你从哪弄来的?
What's wrong with you? Where did you even get that?
约翰尼，你在干什么?
Johnny, what are you doing?
911有什么紧急情况?
9-1-1, what is your emergency?
喂?9-1-1。
Hello? 9-1-1.
你有急事吗?
Do you have an emergency?
先生，你能说话吗?
Sir, can you speak?
如果你不能说话，按手机上的任何按钮。
If you can't speak, press any button on your phone.
一次代表是，两次代表否。
Once for yes, twice for no.
你还在吗?
Are you still there?
先生，请不要挂断，好吗?我会追踪你的位置。
Sir, I want you to stay on the line for me, okay? I'm gonna track your location.
你还在听吗?
Are you still with me?
喂?
Hello?
你还在吗?
Are you still there?
好的，彼得森路129号，迈尔斯县停尸房。
Okay. 129, Peterson Drive, Miles County Morgue.
先生，你还在听吗?
Sir, are you still with me?
坐好，保持冷静。
Just sit tight and remain calm.
警察和医护人员正在赶来的路上
Police and paramedics are on their way...
♬你并不孤单
♪ You're not alone ♪
夫人,我明白了。
Ma'am, I understand.
但我不能给你这个信息。
But I can't give you that information.
保单上只有你丈夫一个人。
Your husband's the only one listed on the policy.
母狗!
Bitch!
不，夫人，不是你。不是你。
No, ma'am, not you. Not you.
妈妈，我们没有卷尺吗?
Mom, don't we have a tape measure?
我不知道。
I don't know.
检查微波炉旁边的抽屉。
Check the drawer by the microwave.
是的,女士!
Yes, ma'am!
我明白，但将来，你丈夫得打电话给保险公司。
I understand that, but in the future, your husband's going to have to call the policy.
我只能告诉你它还在活动。
All I can tell you is that it's still active.
是的。
Yes.
嗯。
Mmhmm.
你能等五分钟，去把你弟弟叫来吗?
Can you wait five minutes, and go get your brother, please?
是的,女士。
Yes, ma'am.
我的经纪人也会跟你说同样的话。
My manager is just gonna tell you the same thing.
你想好明天要穿什么了吗?
So, did you figure out what you're dressing up as tomorrow?
迈尔斯郡的小丑。
The Miles County clown.
-别这么做。——为什么不呢?
- Don't do that. - Why not?
因为这已经超越了不尊重。
Because that's beyond disrespectful.
我们在说什么?
What are we talking about?
他想打扮成去年杀了九个人的真凶。
He wants to dress up as a real guy who murdered nine people last year.
你知道这有多麻木不仁吗?
Do you have any idea how insensitive that is?
更不用说，恶心了。
Not to mention, sick.
-你不能这么做-这只是一套服装
- Oh, you're not doing that. - It's just a costume.
如果上帝保佑，他袭击了我们家的人，而人们为他庆祝，你会作何感想?
How would you feel if God forbid, he attacked someone in our family, and people celebrated him?
这就是你所做的。
That's basically what you're doing.
你不会看到有人打扮成杰弗里·达莫或查尔斯·曼森。
You don't see people dressing up as Jeffrey Dahmer or Charles Manson.
我觉得你们俩都反应过度了。
I think you're both overreacting.
你呢?
Do you?
严格来说，查尔斯·曼森从未杀过人。
Charles Manson technically never killed anyone.
好吧，好吧。足够了。
All right, all right. Enough.
我说，“不”，就这样了。
I said, "No," and that's it.
你知道吗，纳粹曾经给孩子的眼球注射，看他们会不会变色?
Did you know that Nazis used to inject children's eyeballs to see if they would change color?
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
你明天有什么计划?
So, what are your plans tomorrow?
梅根·梅兰妮要办万圣节派对。
Megan Melanie's throwing a Halloween party.
这很好。
That's nice.
你和谁一起去，艾丽?
Who are you going with, Allie?
和布鲁克。
And Brooke.
她不会开车吧?
She's not driving, is she?
我要搭优步。
I'm gonna take an Uber.
为什么，好让你喝得烂醉吗?
Why, so you can get shitfaced?
你以为我是谁，傻瓜，西耶娜?
Who do you think I am, stupid, Sienna?
每次我出去都要这样吗?
Do we have to do this every time I go out?
你知道我不喝酒的。
You know I don't drink.
所以你说。
So you say.
你哥哥从来不合这些该死的盒子。
Your brother never closes these goddamn boxes.
给我。我得到了它。
Give me that. I got it.
妈妈，你有没有…想知道乔纳森吗?
Mom, do you ever... wonder about Jonathan?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你知道,他是……
You know, he's...
-他是个怪人。——所以,什么?
- He's an oddball. - So, what?
我之前去他房间的时候他在查连环杀手。
He was looking up serial killers when I went in his room before.
现在,他是…他说的是纳粹和大屠杀。
Now, he's... he's talking about Nazis and the Holocaust.
——我的意思是……-这只是个阶段，西耶娜
- I mean... - It's just a phase, Sienna.
它会通过。
It'll pass.
你一年前就这么说了。
You said that a year ago.
是啊，他失去了父亲。
Yeah, well, he lost his father.
和我没有?
And I didn't?
你没见过我渴望别人的关注。
You don't see me crying out for attention.
是啊，我有时也希望你这么做。
Yeah, well, I wish you would from time to time.
你把一切都憋在心里。这是不健康的。
You keep everything bottled up. It's not healthy.
好吧。
All right.
如果你在他的房间里发现一只动物的尸体，不要惊讶。
Just don't be surprised if you find a dead animal in his room.
你知道吗?说话客气点，好吗?
You know what? Watch your mouth, huh?
那你呢?
And what about you?
当爸爸带你去钓那些米多或麦多的时候。
When Daddy took you fishing for those midos or macos.
小鱼。
Minnows.
不管他们。
Whatever they're called.
他发现你在砍头。
And he found you cutting the heads off.
你以为我不记得了吗?
Didn't think I'd remember that, did you?
我比乔纳森小得多。
I was a lot younger than Jonathan.
你已经大到能分辨是非了。
Well, you were old enough to know the difference between right and wrong.
你的兄弟很好。
Your brother's fine.
你有强力胶吗?
Do you have any Super Glue?
一点。
A little.
-怎么了，怎么了?-绳子掉了。
- Why, what happened? - The string came off.
我以为你明天不会穿这个。
I thought you weren't gonna wear this tomorrow.
那我就不画脸了。
I won't paint my face then.
——乔纳森。- - - - - -来吧。
- Jonathan. - Come on.
现在换服装太晚了。
It's too late to get another costume.
给我。
Give me.
耶稣。怎么，晚餐后你又长了一只脚吗?
Jesus. What, did you grow another foot since dinner?
我们班最高的孩子。
Tallest kid in my class.
是啊，我还是可以揍你的。
Yeah, well, I can still kick your ass.
不会持续太久。
Not for long.
这是生病。
That is sick.
-你还剩多少钱?-正在完成头骨的制作
- How much do you have left? - Just finishing up the skull.
它看起来就像爸爸的角色。
It looks just like Daddy's character.
你知道吗?
You know?
你现在画得几乎和他一样好了。
You draw almost as good as him now.
谢谢。
Thanks.
这也是你服装的一部分吗?
Is this a part of your costume, too?
不。我不能戴着那东西上街。
No. I could not walk out in the streets with that thing.
我马上就会被逮捕。
I'd get arrested in like two seconds.
是的。但没人会惹你。
Yeah. But nobody would mess with you.
-那当然。——好吧。
- That's for sure. - Right.
请一定要小心。刀片像剃刀一样锋利。
Just be careful, please. That blade's like razor sharp.
给。现在应该没问题了。
There. Should be good now.
太棒了。
Awesome.
你觉得那家伙还逍遥法外吗?
You think that guy's still out there?
谁?
Who?
迈尔斯郡的小丑。
The Miles County clown.
你和这个小丑是怎么回事?
What's up with you and this clown all of a sudden?
你就像着了魔一样。
You're like obsessed.
他们一直没找到他的尸体。
They never found his body.
如果他决定回到这里呢?
What if he decides to come back here?
所以你才想打扮成他的样子吗?
Is that why you wanna dress up like him?
你觉得如果他看到你穿他的戏服，他会对你很友好吗?
You think if he sees you wearing his costume, he'll be all cordial with you?
亲切?
Cordial?
友好。
Friendly.
不。
No.
我不会担心的。
I wouldn't worry about it.
他可能还活着，我敢肯定他已经离开这里很远了。
On the off chance that he is still alive, I'm sure he's gone far away from here.
-再次感谢你的帽子。——不客气。
- Thanks again for the hat. - You're welcome.
利用较低。
Tap lower down.
欧文，我又看到了。
Owen, I saw it again.
嗯?
Hmm?
♬被小丑偶遇café♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♬这个俱乐部简直太可怕了
♪ The club is downright gruesome ♪
但是你的胃口太大了
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
因为食物是有点搞笑，食物是有点搞笑
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny, food's a little funny ♪
♬在小丑的食物有点有趣café♬
♪ Food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
♬路过小丑café，你最喜欢的餐车♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café, your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♬菜单很恶心，但都是特价商品
♪ The menu is disgusting and it's full of special deals ♪
♬这里没有什么对你有好处的，所以自己拿一个托盘
♪ Nothing here is good for you, so grab yourself a tray ♪
因为食物在小丑那里有点搞笑café♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
♬被小丑偶遇café♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
在它跑掉之前，把你的订单加倍
♪ Double up your order quick before it runs away ♪
因为食物在小丑那里有点搞笑café♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
为什么不放学后过来吃点东西呢?♪
♪ Why not visit after school and have yourselves a bite? ♪
♬开胃的开胃菜一定会让人开心
♪ An appetizing appetizer certain to delight ♪
♬我们还没骑过车♬所以，它会让你的牙齿腐蚀♬
♪ We haven't done a ride ♪ And thus, it makes your tooth decay ♪
因为食物在小丑那里有点搞笑café♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
♬被小丑偶遇café♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
这食物实在是太可怕了
♪ The grub is downright gruesome ♪
但是你的胃口太大了
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
因为食物是有点搞笑的食物是有点搞笑的♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny Food's a little funny ♪
♬在小丑的食物有点有趣café♬
♪ Food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
你会帮助这个人吗?
Will you help this man?
你，去那边，喂这个人。
You, over there! Yeah! Feed this man.
你呢?他是饿了。你会喂这个人吗?
How about you? He's hungry. Will you feed this man?
他不是无形的。给他!
He's not invisible. Feed him!
糖梅的新艺术薯片。
New Art Crispies from Sugar Plum.
有趣，每一口都有惊喜。
Fun, little surprises in every bite.
玻璃、昆虫和剃须刀片。
Glass, insects, and razorblade.
谁也不知道你会发现什么!
There's no telling what you may find!
每个盒子里都有特别奖品。
Special prize included in every box.
哇!我想知道我得到了什么!
Wow! I wonder what I got!
说到惊喜，孩子们，我们今天请来了一位非常特别的嘉宾。
Speaking of surprises, kids, we have a very special guest with us today.
作为一个不说话的人，他确实制造了很多噪音。
Now, for a guy who doesn't speak, he sure makes a lot of noise.
让我们欢迎来自迈尔斯县的小丑阿特。
All the way from Miles County, please welcome Art the Clown.
哇!哇!是啊!
Whoo! Whoo! Yeah!
是啊!
Yeah!
停止你正在做的一切!
Stop everything you're doing now!
我看见你们在吃东西。给他!他太饿了。
I see you feeding your faces. Feed him! He's so hungry.
给这个人!给这个人!
Feed this man! Feed this man!
给这个人!
Feed this man!
每个盒子里都有特别奖品。
Special prize included in every box.
大便。
Shit.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
——妈妈!——得到楼下!
- Mom! - Get downstairs!
耶稣基督!
Jesus Christ!
妈妈，你在做什么?来吧!
Mom, what are you doing? Come on!
真的,Sienna?
Really, Sienna?
你整晚都在梳妆台上点蜡烛?
You left burning candles on your dresser all night?
你他妈傻吗?
What are you, fucking stupid?
我什么都没做。他们不是点燃。
I didn't do anything. They weren't lit.
那就跟我解释一下你的房间是怎么着火的。
Then please explain to me how your goddamn room caught on fire.
-我不知道。-你不知道。
- I have no idea. - You have no idea.
所以它是凭空自燃的吗?
So, it just spontaneously combusted out of thin air?
-我想是的。-Sienna…回床上去。你早上还要上学。
- I guess so. - Sienna... Get back to bed. You have school in the morning.
-你是说我还得走?-我说什么了?
- You mean I still have to go? - What did I say?
你知道吗，西耶娜?
You know what, Sienna?
你总有一天会杀了我们的，用你的化学药品和热风枪，熬夜到凌晨4点，鬼知道你在做什么!
You are going to kill us one of these days, between your chemicals and your heat guns, and staying up until 4:00 in the fucking morning doing God only knows what!
哦,我的上帝。我说过一百次了，我没有使用化学药品，也没有在梳妆台上留下燃烧的蜡烛!
Oh, my God. For the hundredth time, I was not using chemicals and I did not leave burning candles on my dresser!
-你为什么就不能相信我?——因为……
- Why can't you just believe me? - Because...
今晚住我房间，我睡沙发。
Stay in my room tonight, and I'll sleep on the couch.
我不介意睡在沙发上。
I don't mind sleeping on the couch.
去睡觉。
Go to bed.
最下面抽屉里的东西我都留着。
I kept whatever was in the bottom drawer.
大部分都毁了。
Most of it's ruined.
回家后一定要把车停在车库里。
Make sure you park in the garage when you get home.
隔壁的那些动物总是扔鸡蛋和剃须膏。
Those animals next door are always throwing eggs and shaving cream.
我不想让车被刮坏。
I don't want the car getting scratched up.
你知道爸爸给我的剑吗?
You know the sword Daddy got me?
什么呢?
What about it?
昨晚还放在我梳妆台上。
It was on top of my dresser last night.
好吧，也许它可以修复。
Well, maybe it can be restored.
是坏的吗?
Is it bad?
它很好。
It's fine.
上面一点痕迹也没有。
There's not a mark on it.
这很好。
That's good.
你的衣服就不一样了。
Can't say the same for your clothes.
乔纳森,快点。你有五分钟的时间。
Jonathan, hurry up. You have five minutes.
欢迎回到我们的节目。
Welcome back to the program.
如果你正在收看，我正在与迈尔斯县大屠杀的唯一幸存者现场直播，就在一年前的今天。
If you're just tuning in, I'm sitting here live with the sole survivor of the Miles County massacre, which occurred exactly one year ago today.
我在这个节目里工作了很多年，我从来没有和一个像你这么有故事的人面对面坐过。
I've worked on the show for many years, and I've never sat across from someone who has a story to tell quite like yours.
再次感谢您花时间坐下来与我交谈。-我的荣幸。
Thank you again for taking the time to sit down - and speak with me. - It's my pleasure.
当我们结束的时候，我们说的是你从昏迷中醒来的那一刻。
Now, when we left off, we were talking about the moment you woke up from the coma.
你还记得你第一次看到你的脸时的第一反应吗?
Do you remember your initial reaction when you first saw your face?
是的。
Yes.
你愿意和我们分享一下吗?
Would you like to share that with us?
我希望我已经死了。
I wished I was dead.
你现在还有这种感觉吗?
Do you still feel that way?
人们会被我的长相吓到，尤其是孩子们。
People are frightened by the way that I look, especially children.
这对我来说真的很难处理，所以隔离是理想的。
And it's really difficult for me to deal with that, so isolation is ideal.
那么袭击者呢?
Now, what about your attacker?
这名男子只被确认为小丑阿特。
The man only identified as Art the Clown.
关于他所谓的死亡有很多争议。
Well, there's a lot of controversy surrounding his supposed death.
当局发表了一份声明，声称他的尸体在袭击发生后的第二天早上从县验尸官办公室消失了。
The authorities issued a statement, claiming that his body disappeared from the county coroner's office the morning after the attack.
他死了。我亲眼看到了。
He's dead. I saw it happen.
-你们在干什么?-伙计，看看肖恩找到了什么
- What are you guys doing? - Dude, look what Sean found.
这是新的吉祥物。
It's the new mascot.
哦,男人。
Oh, man.
正合你胃口，对吧，J兄弟?
Right up your alley, huh, J man?
我想知道它是怎么死的。
I wonder how it died.
可能是吃了学校的烘肉卷。
Probably had the school meatloaf.
我觉得你还是别管了。
I think you should leave it alone.
对什么?他没介意。
What for? He doesn't mind.
它是如此恶心。
It's so gross.
老兄，你应该来的。
Dude, you should have been here.
有几只鸟在吃他的屁眼。
Couple of birds were eating his asshole.
是的。
Yeah.
看这个。斯蒂芬妮!
Watch this. Stephanie!
斯蒂芬妮!过来一下。
Stephanie! Come here for a minute.
肖恩,来吧。
Sean, come on.
一定会很棒的。
It's gonna be awesome.
——怎么了?-看看。
- What's up? - Check it out.
有只猫在垃圾箱后面生了孩子。
Some cat just gave birth behind the dumpster.
——真的吗?-是的。
- Really? - Yeah.
去看看所有的小猫。
Go look at all the kittens.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
怎么了?蛆虫也需要爱!
What's wrong? Maggots need love, too!
斯蒂芬妮!
Stephanie!
你能吗?
Can you?
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
哦,狗屎。普林西比女士。
Oh, shit. Ms. Principe.
你们在这里做什么?
What are you boys doing back here?
哦,基督。亨德森先生。
Oh, Christ. Mr. Henderson.
——什么都没有。——真的吗?
- Nothing. - Really?
你现在就去找柯蒂斯先生，让他把那个搬走。
You go find Mr. Curtis right now, and you have him move that.
你们两个，去上课。
And you two, get to class.
移动它!
Move it!
乔纳森。
Jonathan.
把眼睛盯在自己的纸上。
Keep your eyes on your own paper.
惠伦先生。
Mr. Whalen.
我可以离开一下吗?
May I be excused?
等待。我想我忘带短裤了。
Wait. I think I forgot my shorts.
我想我有一双多余的。
I think I have an extra pair.
你有多余的衬衫吗?——我可能。
- Do you have an extra shirt? - I might.
我们可以去洗手间…
We can go to the bathroom...
嘿!不要在走廊里跑步!
Hey! No running in the hallways!
乔纳森，给我回来!
Jonathan, get back here!
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
万圣节快乐，我的宝贝。
Happy Halloween, my pretty.
-吃巧克力太早了吧?
- Little early for chocolate, no? - Mm.
我可是一个经常吃巧克力伯爵的人。
You're talking to someone who eats Count Chocula on a regular basis.
我们能不谈麦片吗?
Can we not talk about cereal?
好吗?
Please?
好的。
Okay.
今天早上有人心情不好。
Someone's in a mood this morning.
对不起。
Sorry.
昨晚几乎没睡。
Barely slept last night.
让我猜一猜。
Let me guess.
你熬夜到凌晨四点，又在做万圣节服装。
You were up until 4:00 in the morning, working on that Halloween costume again.
实际上，应该是6点。
Actually, it was more like 6:00.
你们听说今早莫妮卡·布朗的事了吗?
Did you guys hear about Monica Brown this morning?
啊!那个恶毒的脱口秀主持人?
Ugh! That bitchy talk show host?
是啊，那个贱人脱口秀主持人的脸完全被扯掉了。
Yeah, that bitchy talk show host totally got her face torn off.
什么?
What?
好的,得到这个。
Okay, get this.
所以她把迈尔斯县的那个幸存者带在身上了。
So, she had that Miles County survivor on.
你还记得那个昏迷不醒脸全是残的人吗?她叫什么名字?
Do you remember the one who was in the coma and her face was all mutilated? What's her name?
就像，我不知道，维多利亚之类的。
It was like, I don't know, Victoria or something.
——维多利亚嘿?——是的。
- Victoria Heyes? - Yes.
她在节目上崩溃了，对吧?
She had a meltdown on the show, right?
然后在后台，她发疯了，徒手撕扯了莫妮卡·布朗。
And then backstage, she went full-on psycho, and mauled Monica Brown with her bare hands.
——没有。-我的天啊。
- No way. - Oh, my God.
她死了吗?
Is she dead?
我是说，如果她够幸运的话。
I mean, if she's lucky.
什么?你见过那些移植面部的照片吗，看起来像土豆头先生?
What? You ever see photos of those transplant faces, looking like Mr. Potato Head?
-去他妈的。-天啊，真的那么糟糕吗?
- Fuck that shit. - God, is it really that bad?
我还没看到照片呢。
Well, I haven't seen photos.
但据我所知，她有点像我饼干里的东西。
But from what I hear, she kinda looks like the inside of my cookie.
她的眼睛全被挖出来了。
Her eyes are all gouged out.
她的鼻子就像从脸上掉下来一样。
And her nose was like falling off of her face.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
我听说她的脸颊有点像，是在维多利亚·海斯的鞋底发现的。
And I heard that her cheek like a little bit, was found at the bottom of Victoria Heyes' shoe.
你没事吧?
You okay?
Sienna?
嘿，你没事吧?
Hey, you all right?
我真的不想用莫妮卡·布朗的破事吓到你。
I really didn't mean to freak you out with that Monica Brown shit.
-很抱歉。——没有。
- I'm so sorry. - No.
——你明白吗?-我没事，我没事我很好。
- You okay? - I'm okay, I'm okay. I'm fine.
我只是…我想我需要点时间。
I just... I just need a second I think.
你好。原谅我。
Hi. Excuse me.
你能管好你自己的事吗?
Can you mind your own business, please?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我的上帝。西耶娜，跟我说话。
My God. Sienna, talk to me.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
我们有…昨晚我们家发生了火灾。
We had... we had a fire last night.
——什么?在哪里?——我的房间。
- What? Where? - My room.
我一定是点着蜡烛睡着了。
I must've fallen asleep with the candles burning.
-非常糟糕。——好的。“相当糟糕”有多糟糕?
- It was pretty bad. - Okay. How bad is "pretty bad"?
就像火焰接触到天花板一样，整座房子都有可能被烧毁。
Like flames touching the ceiling, entire house could have burned down bad.
——耶稣。每个人都好吗?-是的。是的,是的。
- Jesus. Is everyone okay? - Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
不，我妈及时把火扑灭了。
No, my mom put the flames out in time.
哇。他妈的芭芭拉来拯救我们。
Wow. Fucking Barbara to the rescue.
我发誓那女人是个超级英雄。
I swear that woman's a superhero.
-她生气了吗?——愤怒。
- Was she pissed? - Livid.
今天早上训斥了我整整一个半小时。
Berated me for a good hour and a half this morning.
我的意思是，这并不坏。
I mean, that's not so bad.
我是说，你差点在他们睡觉的时候烧了他们全家。
I mean, you did almost torch the whole family in their sleep.
看。重要的是没人受伤。对吧?
Look. The important thing is that nobody got hurt. Right?
说真的，几周后，你会嘲笑整件事的。-更像是几个月。
Seriously, in a few weeks, you'll be laughing - about the whole thing. - More like months.
——好的。几个月。-大概一年吧。
- Okay. A couple months. - Probably a year.
这不仅仅是火灾。
It wasn't just the fire.
它……
It...
昨晚发生了很奇怪的事。
Something really strange happened last night.
什么?
What?
没什么。没什么。我很好。
Nothing. Nothing. I'm fine.
-你确定?-是的。是的。
- You sure? - Yeah. Yeah.
是啊，别这样。嗯…让我们……让我们回去。
Yeah, no, come on. Um... Let's... let's go back.
我的食物可能已经冰凉了。
Now, that my food is probably ice cold.
你想吃我的莫妮卡·布朗饼干吗?
You want a piece of my Monica Brown cookie?
——布鲁克。——对不起。
- Brooke. - Sorry.
我恨你。
I hate you.
谢谢你,警官。
Thank you, Officer.
很抱歉给你带来麻烦。
I'm so sorry to cause you trouble.
没有问题。祝您愉快，女士。
No problem. Have a nice day, ma'am.
你,太。
You, too.
-回你的房间去-但是妈妈，我…回你的房间去。
- Get to your room. - But mom, I... Go to your room.
在我开口之前，我一个字都不想听你说。
I don't wanna hear another word out of you until I say so.
真不敢相信我沦落到只剩下一对廉价的鸡翅了。
I can't believe I'm reduced to a pair of cheap store-bought wings.
你觉得这些太小了吗?
You think these are too small?
你想要多大的?
How big do you want 'em?
你整晚都要打翻别人的饮料什么的。
You're gonna be knocking over people's drinks and shit all night.
我觉得它们很可爱。
I think they're cute.
嗯，他们并不可怕。
Well, they're not terrible.
你没有选择的余地。
You don't really have a choice.
呃，是我妈妈。
Ugh, it's my mom.
你跟你妈说我们今晚要去哪?
Where did you tell your mother we were going tonight?
梅根·梅兰妮的万圣节派对。
Megan Melanie's Halloween party.
好的。我在门口等你。
Okay. I'll catch you out front.
好的。
Okay.
嘿,妈妈。
Hey, Mom.
好。
Good.
不，我和西耶娜在城里。
No, I'm just in town with Sienna.
你什么时候回家?因为…对不起。
What time are you gonna be home? Because... Sorry.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
好了。
Nice.
没什么。我刚碰到一个穿着恐怖小丑服的人。
Nothing. I just ran into a man wearing terrifying clown costume.
我能帮你找点什么吗?
Can I help you find anything?
需要帮忙吗?
Need any help?
一切还好吧?
Uh, find everything okay?
是的。嗯。
Yeah. Mmhmm.
我要扫描一下。
I'm gonna need to scan those.
哦。嗯,对的。对不起。
Oh. Um, right. Sorry.
一切都很好。
It's all good.
好的。这是32.25。
Okay. That'll be 32.25.
是的,嗯…
Yeah, um...
我想我把包落在楼下了。
I think I left my bag downstairs.
先生。
Sir.
如果你要把它放进嘴里，就得付钱。
If you're gonna put that in your mouth, you gotta pay for it.
给你。
Here you go.
谢谢。
Thanks.
你知道吗?我去给你拿个大袋子。
You know what? I'm gonna go get you a big bag.
哦,不,不。我…我真的……-我不…我不需要。-不，不，没关系
Oh, no, no. I... I really... - I don't... I don't need it. - No, no, it's fine.
他们就在我后面。
I got 'em right back here.
好的。
Okay.
请不要。
Please don't.
停。请停止!拜托!
Stop. Please stop! Please!
嘿,哥们?
Hey, buddy?
你不想再惹麻烦了吗?
You wanna quit causin' trouble?
——谢谢。——谢谢。
- Thank you. - Thank you.
——万圣节快乐。——你。
- Happy Halloween. - You, too.
我们要关门了，伙计。
Yo, we closin' up, man.
我能帮你找点什么吗?
Can I help you find something?
8.99.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious right now?
你到底能不能付钱?
Yo, can you pay for that or not?
先生，你在干什么?
Sir, what are you doing?
好的。先生，你知道吗?我要报警了。
All right. Sir, you know what? I'm gonna call the police.
嘿!你听到我说的了吗?
Hey! Did you hear what I said?
在我揍你之前滚出去。
Get the hell outta here before I fuck you up.
这是他妈的疯了。
That's fucking crazy.
我告诉你是他干的，艾莉。
I'm telling you it was him, Allie.
直到他鼻尖上的小黑点。
Right down to the little black dot on the tip of his nose.
西耶娜，你自己说的。
Sienna, you said it yourself.
我是说，今晚会有成百上千的人渣打扮成那个疯子的样子。
I mean, there are gonna be hundreds of douchebags dressed up as that psycho tonight.
连你哥哥都说要扮成他。
Even your brother was talking about going as him.
我不是说你哥哥是混蛋。
Not that I'm calling your brother a douchebag.
这只是个巧合。
It's just a coincidence.
那你怎么解释那场火灾?
Then how do you explain the fire?
我梦见了它，它就发生了。
I dreamt it and it happened.
你最近换过药吗?
Did you change medications recently?
耶稣基督。我不是疯了!
Jesus Christ. I'm not crazy!
换气。
Take a breath.
我…我只是想说，你有没有想过合理的解释也许是火灾导致了你的噩梦，而不是相反?
I... I'm just saying, did you ever consider the logical explanation that maybe the fire caused your nightmare, not the other way around?
什么?
What?
我认为火灾是在你睡觉的时候发生的。
I think that the fire started while you were sleeping.
然后就变成了你的噩梦。
And it worked its way into your nightmare.
我是说，你的身体一定感觉到了火焰。
I mean, your body must've felt the flames.
你知道这种事经常发生。
You know shit like that happens all the time.
听着，你到底要不要糖果?
Look, are you getting candy or what?
我是说，什么是…我们在这里做什么?
I mean, what are... What are we doing here?
即使是这样，也解释不了火灾的起因。
Even if that is the case, it doesn't explain how the fire started.
来吧,亲爱的。
Come on, honey.
哦,我的。他们关闭。
Oh, my. They're closed.
——哇。——哦。
- Wow. - Oh.
看那个，妈妈。
Look at that, Mom.
是啊，太好了，亲爱的。
Yeah, that's wonderful, honey.
酷。
Cool.
好的。我们走吧。我们走吧。
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
你要一直待在这里。
You're just gonna stay here the whole time.
来吧。
Come on.
我们不直接和保险公司联系。
We don't go direct with our insurers.
好吧，让我查查你的邮政编码。
Okay, but let me get your zip code.
我去你那附近找个经纪人。
I'm gonna find a broker in your area.
你在家做什么?
What are you doing home?
他在这里,Sienna
He's here, Sienna.
谁?
Who?
迈尔斯郡的小丑。
The Miles County clown.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我今天在学校看到他了。
I saw him today in my school.
和警方拍的照片一样。
Just like in the police photos.
慢下来。
Slow down.
这是他。
It was him.
今晚会发生很糟糕的事。
Something really bad is gonna happen tonight.
那是爸爸的速写本吗?
Is that Daddy's sketchbook?
看这里。
Look here.
你有这个多久了?
How long have you had this?
乔纳森,回答我。
Jonathan, answer me.
你知道我们找这个找了多久了。
You know how long we've been looking for this.
读这篇文章。
Read this.
我今天见到她了。这个女孩。
I saw her today. This exact girl.
只是她看起来不像人类。
Only she didn't look human.
她，以前的嘉年华，和迈尔斯郡的小丑之间有某种联系。
There's some kinda connection between her, the old carnival, and the Miles County clown.
今晚会发生很糟糕的事。
Something really bad's gonna happen tonight.
我知道它。
I know it.
是你放在这里的吗?
Did you put these in here?
不。
No.
但是看看这个。
But look at this.
这是他!
It's him!
爸爸画这个吗?
Daddy drew this?
这还不是全部。
That's not all.
如果你也有联系呢?
What if you're connected, too?
什么?
What?
乔纳森，你疯了。
Jonathan, you're acting crazy.
你是疯了。好吗?
You're acting crazy. Okay?
他为你创造了这个角色。
He created this character for you.
他临死前把剑给了你。
He gave you that sword right before he died.
他好像早就料到了。
It's like he saw this coming.
爸爸给我画了很多东西。
Daddy drew a lot of things for me.
他给我买了一大堆东西。
He bought me tons of shit.
说真的，你有什么毛病?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
-你知道你在说什么吗?-这是怎么回事?
- Do you even hear yourself? - What's going on in here?
他给你看这个了吗?
Did he show you this?
她不在乎。
She doesn't care.
她只是生气，因为我可能会被停学。
She's just pissed, 'cause I might get suspended.
暂停。为了什么?
Suspended. For what?
哦，你没告诉她?
Oh, you didn't tell her?
你哥哥今早带了只死动物来学校。
Your brother brought a dead animal to school this morning.
——什么?-是的。
- What? - Yeah.
一个死去的动物。你能相信吗?
A dead animal. Can you believe it?
他破坏了大厅。
He vandalized the halls.
他们告诉我的时候，我差点犯心脏病。
I almost had a fucking heart attack when they told me.
这不是我。是小丑。
It wasn't me. It was the clown.
小女孩把它拿了进来。
The little girl brought it in.
我不想再听到关于这个该死的小丑的事。
I don't wanna hear another word about this goddamn clown.
他来的时候，衬衫和手上都是血。
He was covered in blood on his shirt and his hands when he got here.
你被校长当场抓住了。
The principal literally caught you red-handed.
那是因为他朝我扔过来的。
That's 'cause he threw it at me.
我应该听你的。
I should've listened to you.
你跟我说了一遍又一遍关于这孩子的事。
You have been telling me over and over again about this kid.
我周一会给希夫林医生打电话。
I'm calling Dr. Schiffrin on Monday.
我现在要阻止这一切。
I'm putting a stop to this now.
把你那该死的碗放进水槽里。
And put your goddamn bowl in the sink.
我再说一遍。
I'm not telling you again.
这是他。
It was him.
你得相信我。
You gotta believe me.
乔纳森。
Jonathan.
这是……可能只是学校里的几个孩子在胡闹。
It was... It was probably just some kids at school, messing around.
这是一周年纪念。
It's the one-year anniversary.
我是说，我已经看到了一些…一个小时前在《阿布拉卡达布拉》里穿同样衣服的混蛋。
I mean, I already saw some... jerk wearing that same costume in Abracadabra an hour ago.
那么这些图画和文章呢?
What about these drawings and these articles then?
我们都知道爸爸发生了什么。
We both know what happened to Daddy.
这一切都不是他的错。
Okay, none of this was his fault.
这里所有这些丑陋的东西，都不是真正的他。
And all of these ugly things in here, that's not who he was.
他爱你……非常感谢。
He loved you... very much.
会没事的。
It's gonna be okay.
-今晚待在家里。——乔纳森。
- Stay home tonight. - Jonathan.
请。我乞求你。
Please. I'm begging you.
-不会有事的——好。
- Nothing's gonna happen. - Fine.
今晚有人被杀时，别表现得很惊讶。
Just don't act surprised when a bunch of people get killed tonight.
你有没有……
Have you ever...
我相信他。
I believe him.
关于什么?
About what?
我不认为他破坏了学校。
I don't think he vandalized the school.
现在，你相信他了?
Oh, now, you believe him?
昨天，他还是十二宫杀手。
Yesterday, he was the Zodiac Killer.
是什么改变了?
What's changed?
得到了门。
Get the door.
由于最近大肠杆菌爆发，东海岸的餐馆已经召回长叶莴苣。
Restaurants on the East Coast have recalled romaine lettuce due to a recent E. Coli outbreak.
至少12人被送往医院，其中2人伤势严重。
At least 12 people have been hospitalized and two are in critical condition.
-嗨。-不给糖就捣蛋!
- Hi. - Trick or treat!
万圣节快乐。
Happy Halloween.
我喜欢你的妆。
Oh, I love your makeup.
哦，全是她自己做的。
Oh, she did it all herself.
哇!伟大的工作。
Wow! Great job.
你说呢?
What do you say?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
——再见。——再见。
- Bye. - Bye.
你玩不给糖就捣蛋是不是有点老了?
Ah, aren't you a little old to be trick or treating?
等一下。
Wait a minute.
你不是服装店的那个人吗?
Aren't you that guy from the costume shop?
你是谁?
You are?
你在这里做什么?哦。
What are you doing here? Oh.
说真的，你住在这附近吗?
Seriously, do you live around here or something?
嗯。
Hmm.
你真的很奇怪，你知道吗?
You're really weird, you know that?
是的。听着，我明白，伙计。
Yeah. Look, I get it, dude.
整个令人毛骨悚然的默剧噱头。
The whole creepy, silent mime gimmick.
我的意思是，它非常有效。
I mean, it's very effective.
血也是一种很好的触感。
And the blood is a nice touch also.
是的。我不能给你任何东西。
Yeah. I can't give you anything.
不,我很抱歉。真的。不…成年人不吃糖果。
No, I'm sorry. Really. No... no candy for grownups.
来吧。
Come on.
消失。
Go away.
说真的，混蛋，去麻烦别人吧。
Seriously, asshole, go bother somebody else.
你在跟我开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding me right now?
我说了，滚出去。我的意思是它。
I said, get out of here. I mean it.
等待。如果我给你糖果，你就会走吗?
Wait. So, if I give you candy, you'll leave?
很好。
Fine.
在这里。万圣节快乐。
Here. Happy Halloween.
另一则新闻，脱口秀挑衅者，莫妮卡·布朗今晚仍处于生命危险之中，今天早些时候在KLA工作室发生了暴力袭击事件。
In other news, talk show provocateur, Monica Brown is still in critical condition this evening, following a violent attack which took place at KLA Studios earlier today.
这位电视主持人在与嘉宾维多利亚·海斯(Victoria Heyes)进行直播后在更衣室遭到暴力袭击。
The TV host was violently assaulted in her dressing room after a live broadcast with guest Victoria Heyes.
海斯是2017年迈尔斯县大屠杀的唯一幸存者，该事件造成8人死亡，海斯情况危急。
Heyes is the sole survivor of the Miles County massacre of 2017, which left eight people dead and Heyes in critical condition.
这名20岁的男子在犯罪现场被逮捕，并被当局拘留。
The 20-year-old was arrested at the crime scene, and taken into custody by authorities.
考虑到布朗的剥削倾向，该采访一经公布就引发了争议。
The interview sparked controversy upon its announcement given Brown's exploitative tendencies.
经过几个月的康复和精神分析，海耶斯昨晚从圣迈克尔医院出院。
Heyes was released from St. Michael's Hospital yesterday evening after months of rehabilitation and psychoanalysis.
像你,Sienna
Like you, Sienna.
万圣节正式到来了，成千上万的人在纽约东村排队参加游行。
Halloween is officially here, and thousands are lining up for the parade in New York City's East Village.
预计天气将会寒冷多雨，所以如果你打算参加的话，穿暖和点。
Weather conditions are expected to be cold and rainy, so dress warm if you're planning to attend.
不!不!
No! No!
不!
No!
不,不!
No, no!
约翰尼!
Johnny!
你仍然害怕。
You're still afraid.
现在停止。我的意思是它。
Stop it now. I mean it.
他们来抓你了，芭芭拉。
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
好吗?
Well?
停止它!你是无知的。
Stop it! You're ignorant.
他们来抓你了，芭芭拉。
They're coming for you, Barbara.
它是揭示。
It's revealing.
阻止它。
Stop it.
三个月的工作，你只会说它很有启发性吗?
Three months' worth of work, and all you can say is it's revealing?
你的奶子都快露出来了。
Your tits are practically popping out.
他们不是!
They are not!
他们!转身。
They are! Turn around.
他来了。
Here he comes now.
约翰尼!
Johnny!
你知道我在做什么吗?
You know what I was making?
那是爸爸的性格。
It's Daddy's character.
是的，但在纸上看到和在你女儿身上看到是两回事。
Yes, but seeing it on paper and seeing it on your daughter are two different things.
你看起来像是要去脱衣舞俱乐部。
You look like you're going to a strip club.
妈，现在万圣节大家都这么穿。
Mom, this is how people dress on Halloween these days.
你知道我为此花了多少心血吗?
Do you have any idea how much work I put into this?
你做得很好。
You did an excellent job.
但是万圣节什么时候变成了性的代名词?
But when did Halloween become synonymous with sex?
你真是个假正经。
You're such a prude.
好的。这是我的旅程。以后。
Okay. That's my ride. Later.
Sienna.
爸爸会喜欢的。
Dad would have loved it.
再见。
Bye.
艾莉!
Allie!
你发糖果了吗?
Have you been handing out candy?
那碗水还满着呢。
That bowl is still filled to the brim.
艾莉!
Allie!
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
艾莉?
Allie?
艾莉?艾莉,回答我。
Allie? Allie, answer me.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
艾莉?
Allie?
哦，不!不,不!不!不!
Oh, no! No, no! No! No!
妈妈。
Mom.
我怎么跟你说的?
What'd I tell you?
我从未怀疑过你。
I never doubted you for a second.
来吧。我们去爽一爽吧。
Come on. Let's go get fucked up.
你们要点什么?
What can I get you guys?
请给我伏特加和可乐。
Uh, vodka and coke, please.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
手机关机。你想要什么?
Off your phone. What do you want?
呃，朗姆酒和可乐。好坏参半。
Uh, rum and coke. Mixed.
还有，能给我们来两杯威士忌吗?谢谢你！
Also, can we have two shots of whiskey, please? Thank you.
艾莉给你回短信了吗?
Has Allie texted you back yet?
不。
No.
你能查一下吗?
Well, can you check?
负的。
Negative.
你知道这不像她。
You know this isn't like her.
它很好。
It's fine.
只是放松。
Just relax.
好好享受这辈子就这一次，好吗?
And have a good time for once in your life, okay?
也许我给她妈妈发短信，她会给我回复的。
Maybe if I just text her mom, she will get back to me.
不。手机关机。
No. Off your phone.
——手机。——好吧!
- Phone down. - Okay!
-我们会玩得很开心的——嗯。
- Look, we're gonna have fun. - Mmhmm.
——无压力的环境。——是的。
- Stress-free environment. - Yep.
——把这个。——好的。
- Take this. - Okay.
——走吧。——好的。谢谢你！
- Let's go. - All right. Thank you.
我失陪一下好吗?对不起。
Will you excuse me? Sorry.
哦!
Oops!
——走吧。——好的。是的。
- Let's go. - Okay. Yep.
好的。
Okay.
敬我和女儿们度过的美好夜晚。
To a great night with my girls.
-敬一个美好的夜晚。——万圣节快乐。
- To a great night. - Happy Halloween.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
哦，你真是个外行。
Oh, you're such an amateur.
我不知道你是怎么喝那玩意的。
I do not know how you drink that shit.
嗯,追逐它。
Well, chase it.
哦,你混蛋!
Oh, you asshole!
万圣节快乐,宝贝。
Happy Halloween, baby.
你看起来热。
You look hot.
噢,是吗?你喜欢我的发型吗?
Oh, yeah? You like my hair?
我做的事。花了多长时间?
I do. How long did that take?
你不会想知道的。
You don't wanna know.
噢!
Ooh!
是的,不错的衬衫。
Yeah, nice shirt.
一厢情愿的想法。
Wishful thinking.
我敢打赌!
I bet!
哦,杰夫。
Oh, Jeff.
这是我最好的朋友西耶娜。
This is my best friend Sienna.
嗨。
Hi.
哇。这衣服真牛逼。
Wow. That is a badass outfit.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这个女孩非常有才华。
This girl is unbelievably talented.
你不知道。
You have no idea.
从头到脚都是她自己做的。
She made this whole thing herself, head to toe.
你花了多长时间，五个月吗?
What did it take you, like five months?
不。并没有花那么长时间。
No. It didn't take that long.
是的,确实。
Yes, it did.
你不知道。我花了那么长时间。
You have no idea. It took forever.
你是难以置信的。
You are unbelievable.
说实话，我觉得自己被抢了风头。
You know, honestly, I feel upstaged.
好的。
Okay.
你们能别说了吗?
Could you guys please stop?
你让我有点不自在，所以…哦。好吧，喝几杯会有帮助的。
You're making me feel a little self-conscious, so... Oh. Well, a couple of shots will help that.
——哦!镜头!镜头!镜头!镜头!——照片!镜头!镜头!镜头!
- Oh! Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots! - Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
不。不,不,不。今晚我不能再喝了。
No. No, no, no. I cannot drink anymore tonight.
如果我搞砸了，我妈会很生气的。
My mom will get so pissed if I get fucked up.
不,她不会!
No, she won't!
你妈妈两小时后就睡着了。
Your mom's gonna be asleep in two hours.
我做不到。
I can't do it.
好的,很好。
Okay, fine.
给我们照张相。
Take a picture of us.
好的。
Okay.
哦,让我们跳舞吧!
Ooh, let's dance!
好的。
Okay.
-不给糖就捣蛋!-不给糖就捣蛋!
- Trick or treat! - Trick or treat!
孩子们，多酷啊!
Kids, look how cool!
哦我的上帝!
Oh my God!
太酷了。
So cool.
为什么我的这么黏?
Ew. Why is mine so sticky?
别担心。这只是假血。
Don't worry. It's just fake blood.
把它放进袋子里就行了。
Just put it in the bag.
哦，我喜欢。
Ooh, I like it.
好的，谢谢!
All right, thank you!
——谢谢!——谢谢!
- Thank you! - Thank you!
我们走吧。万圣节快乐!
Let's go. Happy Halloween!
——万圣节快乐!——万圣节快乐!
- Happy Halloween! - Happy Halloween!
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing in here?
你想看电影吗?
You wanna watch a movie?
楼下有很多剩下的糖果。
There is a lot of candy leftover downstairs.
来吧。我允许你熬夜。
Come on. I'll let you stay up late.
消失。
Go away.
乔纳森。
Jonathan.
很抱歉你今晚的计划被毁了。
I am sorry that your plans were ruined tonight.
我真的害怕。
I really am.
但你今天在学校做那些事之前就该想到这一点。
But you should've thought about this before you pulled that shit in school today.
我是说，受够了。
I mean, enough's enough.
我说的都是实话。
I told you the truth.
-我不会再这么做了。-不是我!
- I'm not doing this again. - It wasn't me!
如果不是你，那我真心道歉。
Well, if it wasn't you, then I sincerely apologize.
但我再也不相信你了。
But I just don't believe you anymore.
这是什么?
What about this?
又是这本该死的书!
Again with this fucking book!
爸爸为什么要收集这些新闻文章?
Why was Daddy collecting these news articles?
"嘉年华发现被害女孩"这吗?
"Slain girl found at carnival." And this?
看看这些图画!
Look at these drawings!
这可不像爸爸!
This isn't like Daddy!
他生病了。
He was sick.
你为什么不明白?
Why can't you understand?
他不知道自己是谁，也不知道自己在做什么。
He didn't know who he was, or what he was doing half the time.
这。
And this.
这他妈只是个提醒。
This bullshit is nothing but a fucking reminder.
不!
No!
我要这东西从我家里滚出去。
I want this out of my house.
你真是个贱人!
You're such a bitch!
不准你再对我说这种话!
Don't you ever say that to me again!
乔纳森。乔纳森，你给我回来
Jonathan. Jonathan, you get back here.
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
等待。你要去哪里?
Wait. Where are you going?
我去喝一杯。
I'm gonna grab a drink.
-能给我张自拍吗?——确定。
- Yo, can I get a selfie? - Sure.
他妈的,是的,女孩!
Fuck, yeah, girl!
什么?
What?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
Sienna!
——嘿!——你好!
- Hey! - Hi!
我想你了，姑娘。
I missed you, girl.
嗨。
Hi.
不,等等。
No, wait.
——觉得这。——哦。
- Feel this. - Oh.
哦。
Oh.
-我的天啊。——不,不。等待。
- Oh, my God. - No, no. Wait.
你不明白。我想要它。
You don't understand. I want it.
——我知道。-我想…生活在其中，你知道吗?
- I know. - I wanna like... live in it, you know?
-你感觉怎么样?——好。
- How are you feeling? - Good.
是吗?
Yeah?
-实际上非常好!——好的。
- So good actually! - Okay.
我觉得……这一枪真的开始击中我了。
I feel like... that shot's really starting to hit me.
威士忌会让你变成这样的。
Well, whiskey will do that to you.
-我需要这个。-是的。
- I needed this. - Yeah.
你是对的。
You were right.
-你说得太对了-是的。
- You were so right. - Yeah.
我需要出去走走，不再去想，不再去担心生活中的每一件小事。
I needed to just, like get out, and stop thinking, worrying about every little thing in my life.
喜欢……这样的服装。
Like... like this costume.
是的。
Yeah.
我是说，这应该是件快乐的事。
I mean, it should be a happy thing.
-是的。——你知道吗?
- Yeah. - You know?
这让我想起了我爸爸。
It reminds me of my Dad.
他过去……当我还是个小女孩的时候，他经常给我画这个角色。
He used to... He used to draw this character for me when I was a little girl.
他曾告诉我，我长大后会像她一样。
He used to tell me I was gonna grow up to be like her one day.
我真的相信了。
And I really believed it.
看看你现在的样子!
Well, look at you now!
你是她的。
You are her.
我一点也不像她。
I am nothing like her.
我不勇敢。
I'm not courageous.
I'm not brave.
我今天真的在学校里恐慌症发作了当着大家的面。
I mean, I literally had a panic attack today in school in front of everybody.
我在你的饮料里放了莫利。
I put molly in your drink.
什么?
What?
我做到了。我在你的酒里放了半片，我的酒里放了半片。
I did. I put a half a tablet in your drink, the other half in mine.
也不是真的，没什么大不了的。
Not even really, it was kind of nothing.
但没关系，因为我也在上面。
But it's fine, 'cause I'm also on it.
所以，我们完全没问题。你和我。
So, we're totally fine. You and me.
所以你才会觉得自己磕了摇头丸。
And that is why you feel like you're on molly.
因为你。
'Cause you are.
现在。
Right now.
你他妈的婊子!
You fuckin' bitch!
什么……-太糟糕了!-我做到了。
What the... - That is so messed up! - I did it.
我让你感觉好点了，不是吗?
I made you feel better, didn't I?
我他妈的很生气。
I'm fucking pissed.
不，别生气。
No, don't be pissed.
你微笑。你不能生气。
You're smiling. You can't be pissed.
不,婊子。我不微笑。
No, bitch. I'm not smiling.
你完全微笑。
You're totally smiling.
所以，我们要回去，我们要跳舞。
So, we gotta go back out, and we gotta dance.
乔纳森。
Jonathan.
乔纳森，请回去。
Jonathan, please get back.
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
什么?
What?
我妈给我打了六次电话。
My mom called me like six times.
——哦。不要给她回电话。-我要去看…-别给她回电话!嘘，嘘，嘘!
- Ooh. Do not call her back. - I'm gonna see... - Don't call her back! - Shh, shh, shh!
Sienna. Sienna.
——Sienna。——嘿!
- Sienna. - Hey!
——停。-他死了，西耶娜!
- Stop it. - He's dead, Sienna!
等待。什么?
Wait. What?
切断了电话。
Cut the call.
等一下,妈妈。妈妈，我听不见。
Wait, mom. Mom, I can't hear you.
只是…嗯,抱歉。
Just... Um, sorry.
嗯，你说什么?
Um, what'd you say?
他把整辆车都涂满了剃须膏!
He covered the entire fucking car with shaving cream!
什么?
What?
是啊!整件该死的事。
Yeah! The whole fucking thing.
剃须膏，厕纸，鸡蛋。他死了!
Shaving cream, toilet paper, eggs. He's dead!
他……乔纳森不会这么做的。
He... Jonathan wouldn't do that.
是的。不是他干的。
Yeah. He didn't do this.
就像他今早没有破坏学校一样!
Just like he didn't vandalize the school this morning!
看看这个。不，不，不，不，不。
Look at this. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
这个…这太疯狂了。
This... this is crazy now.
他马上就去看心理医生。
He's going to that psychiatrist immediately.
我再也受不了他了。
I cannot deal with him anymore.
妈妈,真的吗?
Really, mom?
你要送他去看心理医生就因为他在你车上抹了一点剃须膏吗?
You're gonna send him to a shrink because what, he put like a little bit of shaving cream on your car?
我很高兴你觉得这很有趣，西耶娜。
I'm glad you think this is funny, Sienna.
只是剃须膏而已。
It's just shaving cream.
他又没拿棒球棒砸你的挡风玻璃。
It's not like he took a baseball bat to your windshield.
这是万圣节。我的意思是……你喝醉了吗?
It's Halloween. I mean... Are you drunk?
——没有。-不，你是。
- No. - Yes, you are.
我能从你的声音里听出来。你喝了多少酒?
I can hear it in your voice. How many drinks have you had?
我…我以为我们说的是乔纳森。
I... I thought we were talking about Jonathan.
西耶娜，帮我个忙，如果你回家时满身是泥——我今晚要处理的事情……——没有。
Sienna, so help me, if you come home plastered on top of everything else - I'm dealing with tonight... - No.
我对天发誓，我没醉。我甚至可以做个酒精测试。
I swear to God, I'm not drunk. I'll even take a breathalyzer.
我杀死你。
You're killing me.
你知道吗?
You know that?
你和你哥哥，我受够了。
You and your brother both, I have had it.
我爱你。
I love you.
是的，西耶娜，我警告你。
Yeah, Sienna, I am warning you.
不。妈妈,真的。
No. Really, mom.
我…我爱你。我…
I... I love you. I...
我说得不够多。
I don't say it enough.
我也爱你。
I love you, too.
去享受你的聚会吧。我…很抱歉打扰你。
Go and enjoy your party. I'm... I'm sorry to bother you.
和听。
And listen.
乔纳森会没事的。
Everything will be okay with Jonathan.
我保证。
I promise.
记住我说的话。
Just remember what I said.
回家的时候小心点，好吗?
Be careful getting home, all right?
我会的。再见。
I will. Bye.
娘,万圣节快乐!
Happy Halloween, motherfuckers!
-怎么样?——好。
- How'd it go? - Fine.
好吧。
All right.
我来给你讲点莫莉的规矩。
Let me give you a little molly etiquette here.
第一条规矩，当你吸了莫利的时候千万别打电话给你妈。
Rule number one, you never ever call your mother when you're rolling on molly.
好吧?你的母亲,从来没有。好吧?
Okay? Your mother, never. All right?
第二条，你他妈不能浪费时间。来吧。
Rule number two, you don't fucking let it go to waste. Come on.
看看这个。
Look at this.
他真的以为自己能逃脱惩罚吗?
Did he really think he was gonna get away with this?
他将会猛然醒悟。
He is in for a rude awakening.
事情会改变的。
Things are gonna change.
♪痛，总是痛
♪ Pain, always pain ♪
♪痛苦造就了节奏，♪造就了节奏
♪ Pain makes the rhythm, makes the rhythm ♪
让节奏变得♬♬
♪ Makes the rhythm ♪
♪痛苦，痛苦造就了节奏，痛苦造就了节奏
♪ Pain, pain makes the rhythm, makes the rhythm ♪
让♪节奏，让♪痛苦
♪ Makes the rhythm, pain ♪
你看到了吗?
Do you see that?
那里。那个小女孩。
There. There. That little girl.
她在说什么?
What is she saying?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我…我…我对天发誓。
I... I... I swear to God.
她就在那里。我…我看见她了。
She was right there. I... I saw her.
她…她就在那里。
She was... She was... she was right there.
好的。来吧。这是浴室。
Okay. Come on. It's bathroom time.
Sienna? Sienna?
好的。西耶娜，看着我。没关系。嘘,嘘,嘘。
Okay. Sienna, look at me. It's okay. Shh, shh, shh.
Sienna,呼吸。呼吸。呼吸。你会没事的。
Sienna, breathe. Breathe. Breathe. You're gonna be okay.
Sienna?
妈妈!
Mom!
帮帮我!
Help me!
很遗憾你不得不离开。
I'm sorry you had to leave.
这是没有问题。
It's no problem.
你没事吧?
You okay?
西耶娜，刚才是怎么回事?
Sienna, what the fuck was that back there?
我很好。
I'm fine.
你他妈开什么玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding me?
不!你不是很好。
No! You're not fine.
你现在一点都不好。
You are so completely far from fine right now.
你完全被吓坏了。
You're just totally freaked out.
哎呀,布鲁克。我想知道为什么。
Gee, Brooke. I wonder why.
哦!别怪我。
Oh! Don't blame this on me.
我现在和你处境一样，好吗?
I'm on the same shit as you right now, okay?
-我没有害怕。——哇!
- I'm not freaking out. - Whoa!
我们在这里说什么?什么狗屎?
What are we talking about here? What shit?
我在她的饮料里放了一点莫利。
I put a pinch of molly in her drink.
没什么。
It was nothing.
- +阿普唑仑。——什么?
- Plus Xanax. - What?
我没有给你阿普唑仑。
I did not give you Xanax.
不，她已经在吃阿普唑仑了，我不知道，好吗?
No, she was already on Xanax, which I didn't know about, okay?
让我们把话说清楚。
Let's make that perfectly fucking clear.
你差点杀了我。
You could've fucking killed me.
我只是想为你做点好事。
I was trying to do something nice for you.
耶稣基督!
Jesus Christ!
你一直都像个病态女士。
You're like Ms. Morbid all the time.
谢谢。
Thanks.
送我回家吧。
Just take me home.
西耶娜，刚才发生的事不正常。
Sienna, whatever happened back there was not normal.
好吗?
Okay?
你可能得了脑动脉瘤，或者癫痫发作之类的。
You could have had like a brain aneurysm, or seizure, or something.
如果再发生这种事怎么办?
What if it happens again?
要送她去急诊室吗?
Wanna take her to the emergency room?
我…我只是…我只想回家。
I... I just... I just wanna go home.
送我回家吧。
Just take me home.
如果是你妈妈打来的，别接。
If that's your mother, do not answer it.
你好。
Hello.
西耶娜，我有麻烦了。
Sienna, I'm in trouble.
哦,你觉得呢?
Oh, you think?
妈妈告诉我你对她的车做了什么，你个小混蛋。
Mommy told me what you did to her car, you little asshole.
我的意思是,真的吗?
I mean, really?
不。我需要你的帮助。
No. I need your help.
你得来接我。
You have to come get me.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你在哪里?
Where are you?
我在以前的狂欢节上。
I'm at the old carnival.
埃里克和肖恩把我丢在这里了。我独自一人。
Eric and Sean left me here. I'm all alone.
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
请。我真的害怕。
Please. I'm really scared.
我不知道还能怎么办。我不能给妈妈打电话。
I don't know what else to do. I can't call mommy.
好的。嗯,好吧。冷静下来。
Okay. Um, all right. Calm down.
我去接你，好吗?
I'll come get you, okay?
快点，我手机快没电了。
Hurry, my phone is dying.
好的。在正门等着，好吗?
All right. Just wait by the main entrance, okay?
乔纳森吗?乔纳森吗?J……该死。
Jonathan? Jonathan? J... Goddammit.
他是胡说。
He's bullshitting you.
不,他不是。
No, he's not.
是的,他是。
Yes, he is.
这是万圣节。
It's Halloween.
你现在是在告诉我你哥哥做这种扭曲的事有失身份吗?来吧。旧的狂欢节。
Are you really telling me right now that it's beneath your brother to do something twisted like this? Come on. The old carnival.
不。我…我知道乔纳森在撒谎。好吗?
No. I... I know when Jonathan's lying. Okay?
我…我能从他的声音里听出来。
I... I could hear it in his voice.
……有点不对劲
Something's... something's wrong.
Sienna!像,伙计…离这里只有几英里。
Sienna! Like, dude... It's only a few miles from here.
这太蠢了。
This is so stupid.
太好了。好吧。无论什么。我也不在乎
Great. Fine. Whatever. I don't care.
今晚也不会更糟了。
It's not like this night can get any worse.
他在哪里?
Well, where is he?
我叫他在前面等着。
I told him to wait in front.
-你哥哥多大了?- 12。
- How old's your brother? - 12.
即使是他现在在外面的事实也应该告诉你一些事情。
Even the fact that he's out here right now should be telling you something.
几年前不是有个小女孩在这里被杀了吗?
Didn't like a little girl get murdered out here a couple years ago?
我去找他。
I'm gonna go look for him.
什么?
What?
Sienna?回到车里去。
Sienna? Get back in the car.
Sienna!
她疯了。
She's crazy.
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
也许我们应该和她一起去。
Maybe we should go with her.
他妈的。我向你保证，她哥哥会把她吓得屁滚尿流。
Fuck that. I guarantee you, her brother's just gonna scare the shit out of her.
自从他父亲自杀后，他就完全变成了一个疯子。
He's turned into a complete psycho ever since his father killed himself.
自从什么?
Ever since what?
没有玩笑。
No joke.
他长了个巨大的脑瘤，我不知道，这让他做了所有该死的事。
He had like this giant brain tumor that I don't know, it just made him do all this fucked-up shit.
他好像看到了一些东西。
And he was like seeing things.
到最后他变得很粗暴。
And he got really abusive towards the end.
尤其是对Sienna
Especially towards Sienna.
然后有一天，他喝了一整瓶杰克威士忌，然后上了车，直接撞到了一个变压器什么的。
And then one day, he drank a whole bottle of Jack, and he got in his car, and he drove straight into one of those transformer things.
车着火了，他被困在了残骸里。
And the car caught fire, and he got trapped in the wreck.
他被烧死了
And he burned to death.
你在一英里外都能听到他的尖叫。
You could hear him screaming from a mile away.
我认识你朋友才几个小时，但这就解释了很多事。
Well, I've only known your friend for a few hours, but that explains a lot.
是的。
Yeah.
总的来说，我认为她做得很好。
All things considered, I think she's doing pretty well.
来，回答我。
Come on, answer me.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
我正在到处找。
I'm searching all over the place.
的帮助。
Help.
乔纳森，你能听到我说话吗?
Jonathan, can you hear me?
我不能……听。
I can't... Listen.
我在旋转木马旁等你，好吗?
I'm gonna wait for you by the merry-go-round, okay?
你听到我说的了吗?
Did you hear what I said?
在旋转木马那儿等我。
Meet me at the merry-go-round.
喂?
Hello?
回复我的短信。
Text me back.
那是什么?
What is that?
有点提神饮料。
A little pick-me-up.
哇,杰夫。好的。
Wow, Jeff. Okay.
别让西耶娜看到。
Don't let Sienna see that shit.
我们得在她回来之前搞定。
Well, we'll just have to do it before she comes back.
我不会那么做的。
I'm not doing that.
你试过吗?
You ever try it?
是的。一次。我不喜欢它。
Yeah. Once. I didn't like it.
哦,当然,不可能的。来吧。
Oh sure, impossible. Come on.
这能让我们重回俱乐部。
This will put us right back in the club.
他妈的。
Fuck.
相信我。
Trust me.
好的。
Okay.
好的。他妈的。
All right. Fuck it.
嗯…好吧。
Um... okay.
啊!
Ugh!
这尝起来怪怪的。
That tastes weird.
乔纳森吗?
Jonathan?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
她到底在哪里?
Where the hell is she?
谁在乎呢?
Who cares?
等待。
Wait.
好的。但是，说真的，她什么时候走的?
All right. Look, but, like, seriously, what time did she leave?
-谁在乎啊?——好的。
- Well, who cares? - Okay.
好的。我马上打给她，好吗?
Okay. I'm gonna call her really fast, okay?
真的快。
Just really quick.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
我要去尿尿。
I have to go pee-pee.
你想拿着吗?
You wanna hold it?
走吧
Ew. Leave.
你好。是Sienna
Hi. It's Sienna.
请留言，我会给你回电。
Leave a message, and I'll get back to you.
邮箱满了…难以置信。
The mailbox is full... Unbelievable.
目前无法接受任何消息。
And cannot accept any messages at this time.
再见……混蛋!
Goodbye... Asshole!
这是两次!
That's twice!
哦，太有趣了。
Oh, it's so funny.
是啊，你太有趣了。
Yeah, you're so funny.
你知道真正有趣的是什么吗?
You know what's actually really funny?
-嗯-嗯
- Mm. - Mm.
让我看看。哦。
Let me see here. Oh.
哦,嘿。别惹她。
Oh, hey. Don't fuck her up.
- - - - - -来吧。——哦。
- Come on. - Oh.
-哦，你最好道歉。——我很抱歉。
- Oh, you better say sorry. - I'm sorry.
我不知道你能不能从烟灰缸里吸出这个。
And I don't really know if you can snort this out of an ashtray.
要吸出去有点难。
It'd be kinda hard to snort out of.
我很抱歉!我很抱歉!我不会再犯了，我保证。
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I won't do it again, I promise.
你真的很抱歉吗?
Are you actually sorry?
嘿。
Hey.
好的,很好。
Okay, fine.
但你是个混蛋。
But you're a jerk.
杰夫?
Jeff?
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
不!不,不!
No! No, no!
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
Sienna!
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
Sienna!
哦,我的上帝!哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
你能听到我说话吗?
Can you hear me?
来人!
Somebody, please!
救命!
Help me!
Sienna!
救命!
Help!
布鲁克!
Brooke!
哦,我的上帝!不,请!不!
Oh, my God! No, please! No!
待回来。停。请停止。离我远点!
Stay back. Stop. Please stop. Stay away from me!
不,谢谢!
Don't, please!
等待,等待。不!请,请停止!不!
Wait, wait. No! Please, please stop! No!
不，不，不，不!阻止它。停。不。拜托!
No, no, no, no! Stop it. Stop. No. Please!
不。待回来。不要……别靠近我。
No. Stay back. Don't... don't come near me.
请不要。不,不,不!
Please don't. No, no, no!
布鲁克!
Brooke!
布鲁克。
Brooke.
乔纳森?
Jonathan?
乔纳森,快跑!
Jonathan, run!
来吧。
Come on.
这里
This way.
Sienna.
你受伤了。
You're hurt bad.
我一切都好。我一切都好。让我……让我看看你。
I'm all right. I'm all right. Let me... let me see you.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你是对的。
You were right.
你说的都对。
You were right about everything.
我对你的看法也是对的。
I was right about you, too.
关于什么?
About what?
他们利用我把你带到这里。
They used me to get you here.
他们需要你在这里是有原因的。
They need you in this place for a reason.
你在说什么?
What are you saying that?
这是爸爸看到的。
It's what Daddy saw.
我觉得你是唯一能阻止他的人。
I think you're the only one who can stop him.
为什么?
Why?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我们得想办法出去。
Well, we gotta find a way out of here.
好吧,来吧。
Okay, come on.
在这等着。
Wait here.
乔纳森。
Jonathan.
笨蛋!
Sucker!
乔纳森·…
Jonathan...
Sienna!
Sienna,醒醒。
Sienna. Sienna, wake up.
和我呆在一起。留在我身边!请不要走。
Stay with me. Stay with me! Please don't go.
Sienna。请不要离开我。
Sienna. Please don't leave me.
Sienna。宝贝,醒了。
Sienna. Baby, wake up.
妈妈?
Mom?
亲爱的,没关系。
Sweetie, it's okay.
你是安全的。
You're safe.
妈妈。
Mom.
哦，嘘，嘘，嘘。
Oh, shh, shh, shh.
一切都会没事的。
Everything's gonna be okay.
我以为再也见不到你了。
I thought I was never gonna see you again.
哦。
Oh.
约拿单告诉你…不是吗?
Jonathan told you... didn't he?
什么?
What?
Sienna!
离她远点!那不是妈妈!
Get away from her! That's not Mommy!
乔纳森!
Jonathan!
不!不!
No! No!
不!不,你塔克!
No! No, you tucker!
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
说到奖品，孩子们，今天我们请来了一位非常特别的嘉宾。
Speaking of some prizes, kids, we have a very special guest with us today.
让我出去!
Let me out!
-♬小丑来吧café♬-♬小丑来吧café♬
- ♪ Come on by the clown café ♪ - ♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
♬这个俱乐部简直太可怕了
♪ The club is downright gruesome ♪
但是你的胃口太大了
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
因为食物有一点搞笑食物有一点搞笑
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny food's a little funny ♪
♬在小丑的食物有点有趣café♬
♪ Food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
Sienna!
Sienna.
你抓到他了。
You got him.
都结束了。好吗?
It's over now. Okay?
好的。
Okay.
请告诉我这是南瓜香料。
Please tell me this is pumpkin spice.
绝对不可能。
Not a chance in hell.
这是什么?
What is this?
僵尸盘。我妻子做的。
Zombie platter. My wife made it.
这是恶心。
That's disgusting.
有创意,但恶心。
Creative, but disgusting.
你没试过之前我可不会这么说。
I wouldn't say that before you try it.
它很好吃。
It's pretty tasty.
不,谢谢。
Mm. No, thanks.
尽管那个大脑看起来很吸引人，但我现在真的没胃口。
As appealing as that brain looks, I don't really have the stomach for it right now.
一切都好吗?
Everything okay?
我一整天都在照顾我们的名人病人。
I've been tending to our celebrity patient all day.
是坏的吗?
Is that bad?
这么说吧，她的脸不能激发人的食欲。
Let's just say her face doesn't stimulate one's appetite.
-她长得怎么样?——驯服。
- What's she like? - Tame.
非常合作。
Pretty cooperative actually.
很难想象她会把那个女人撕成碎片。
It's kind of hard to imagine she ripped that woman to pieces.
给我一个眼球。
Pass me one of those eyeballs.
嗯?
Huh?
再涂点脑胶在上面。
And, uh, put some of that brain jelly on it, too.
还有，萝拉，别小气。哦。在这里。那就这样吧。
And, Lola, don't be stingy. Oh. There it is. There you go.
更多。
Little more.
谢谢你！明天开始节食，所以…
Thank you. Diet starts tomorrow, so...
-那是什么?——嗯?
- What is that? - Hmm?
你唱的那首歌是什么?
That song you're singing, what is it?
哦。
Oh.
我也不知道。
I have no idea actually.
维多利亚已经唱了一整天了。
Victoria's been singing it all day.
我一直在想这件事。
I can't get it out of my head.
嗯。
Huh.
♬来吧，小丑café♬
♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
你他妈的婊子!
You fucking cunt!
♬来吧，小丑café♬
♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
女人!女人!女人!女人!女人!
Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
♬路过小丑café你最喜欢的餐车♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♬菜单很恶心，但都是特价商品
♪ The menu is disgusting and it's full of special deals ♪
♬这里没有什么东西对你有好处，所以自己拿一个托盘
♪ Nothing here is good for you so grab yourself a tray ♪
因为食物在小丑那里有点搞笑café♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny at the clown café ♪
♬被小丑偶遇café♬
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
在它跑掉之前，把你的订单加倍
♪ Double up your order quick before it runs away ♪
因为食物在小丑那里有点搞笑café♬
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny at the clown café ♪